

JOHN CARLO FABABEIR

Portfolio: <u>jcavenue.github.io</u>

PROFILE

I am an Aspiring Software Developer have more than 1-year experience as a self-taught web developer.

SKILLS

Programming Languages and Database

PHP, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, PostgreSQL, SQL, MySQL

Frameworks and Tools

Cypress, React, Redux, MDBootstrap, Bootstrap, Git, GitHub, Visual Studio Code, Figma, CLI,

LICENSES AND CERTIFICATION

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

Issued September 2021 – Expire 2024

CONTACT



jcfababeir30@gmail.com



+63-963-3218-452



linkedin/in/jcfababeir

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Quality Assurance Intern

Achieve Without Borders – Makati (WFH)
October 2021 – Present

- Perform Manual Testing
- Create Test Automation Using Cypress
- Execute Regression Testing
- Create Test Scenario

Graphic Assistant

Kent Graphic Solution October 2018 - March 2019

Email Support Representative

SPi CRM Inc, now INSPIRO April 2018 - August 2018

Factory Worker

Traditional Food Corporation Jan 2016 - October 2016

EDUCATION

ASIAN INSTITUTE OF COMPUTER STUDIES

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science 2019 - Present

BAGONG SILANGAN HIGH SCHOOL

Secondary Education 2009 - 2013

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITY

Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador (Alpha Member) July 2021

Global Student Leaders